Boston School of Occupational Therapy (BSOT) Records UA032
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audiovisual materials, 1920 -- 1995; 1930 -- 1995; UA032.009; 11.55 Linear Feet; 31 Digital Object(s)
  - Photographs, 1920 -- 1978; UA032.009.001
    - Graduation, 1906 -- 1949; UA032.009.019.00013 (Box 19)
      - Capping ceremony for BSOT Class of 1949, 1906 -- 1949; UA032.009.019.00013.00001; Loesch, Russell T. (Box 19)
        Photo marked: Tufts 1949. Class A.C. 39 - 1947-1949.
        Students; Rites and ceremonies; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Class Pictures, 1952; UA032.009.019.00014 (Box 19)
      - BSOT Class of 1952, UA032.009.019.00014.00001; Egan Photo Service (Box 19)
        Photo marked: Tufts 1952 - A.C. 1952. Front row (left to right): June Fairneny, Suzanne Johnson, Judith Kahnm Joanne Plimpton, Anita Teller, Dorothy Beckler, and Helen Nolan. Second row: Mary Wold, Priscilla Alden, Virginia Gary, Mary Wilson, Mildred Dexter, Leona Cox, Stephanie Wong, Abigail Demord, and Joan Crawford. Back row: Philippa Grover, Jeanne Custato, Alice Jantzen, Muriel Omdahl, Carlos Gonzales, Bonnie-Jean Bird, Paula Vose, and Virginia Auty.
    - Graduation, 1950; UA032.009.019.00015 (Box 19)
    - Fritz Kreisler concert poster, director of BSOT, Mrs. John A. Greene, in attendance, 1940 -- 1950; UA032.009.019.00016 (Box Shared 46)
      These dates are approximate. This item was found uncataloged in the stacks in the winter of 2009. Note the different location of this item; it is housed in a box with other oversize materials.
    - A.O.T.A Conventions, 1951 -- 1955; UA032.009.109.00001 (Box 109)
    - Graduations, 1951; UA032.009.109.00002 (Box 109)
    - Registration and Graduation, 1951 -- 1952; UA032.009.109.00003 (Box 109)
      Photographs taken by Veronica Cavanaugh Dobranske, class of 1936
    - Exhibits, 1953; UA032.009.109.00004 (Box 109)
    - Graduation, 1953; UA032.009.109.00005 (Box 109)
    - Trustees Dinner, 1954; UA032.009.109.00006 (Box 109)
    - Graduation, 1955; UA032.009.109.00007 (Box 109)
    - Proofs and Photos for catalogs, 1962 -- 1967; UA032.009.109.00008 (Box 109)
    - Members of Defense Advisory Committee on Women in the Services, 1962; UA032.009.109.00009 (Box 109)
    - "Two Hands Are Better Than One", 1959; UA032.009.109.00010 (Box 109)
      PBS Broadcast regarding BSOT and Occupational Therapy
    - Graduation, 1967; UA032.009.109.00011 (Box 109)
    - A.O.T.A. Golden Anniversary, 1967; UA032.009.109.00012 (Box 109)
      Reception for West- Slagle, Wilma (lecturer)
    - Graduation, 1970; UA032.009.109.00013 (Box 109)
    - Greene, Margorie Belle, 1920; UA032.009.109.00014 (Box 109)
    - Lovell General Hosptial, 1944; UA032.009.109.00015 (Box 109)
    - Dobranske, Veronica Cavanaugh, 1948; UA032.009.109.00016 (Box 109)
    - Reggio, Dr. and Marble, Henry, 1951; UA032.009.109.00017 (Box 109)
    - 50th anniversary banquet, 1968; UA032.009.141.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 141)
      5x7 prints.
    - 50th anniversary banquet, 1968; UA032.009.141.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 141)
      Test strips.
    - 50th anniversary banquet - dining, 1968; UA032.009.141.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 141)
    - 50th anniversary banquet - student exhibitions, 1968; UA032.009.141.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 141)
    - 50th anniversary banquet - group photographs, 1968; UA032.009.141.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 141)
    - 50th anniversary banquet - speeches, 1968; UA032.009.141.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 141)
    - 50th anniversary banquet - awards, 1968; UA032.009.141.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 141)
    - Group photographs, 1955 -- 1965; UA032.009.141.00009; Fay Foto (Box 141)
      This is a photograph of Mr. George Storia, Dr. William Berenberg, Mrs. Veronica Dobranske, and Dr. Philip Cashman.
    - Patients at loom, 1920 -- 1945; UA032.009.141.00010 (Box 141)
      Dates are approximate.
    - Jean Davis and patient, 1945; UA032.009.141.00011 (Box 141)
    - Woodworking photographs, 1945; UA032.009.141.00012 (Box 141)
    - Child with doll, 1945; UA032.009.141.00013 (Box 141)
      Date is approximate.
    - Liberty Mutual Rehab Center, 1945; UA032.009.141.00014 (Box 141)
    - Patient examinations, 1945; UA032.009.141.00015 (Box 141)
    - Women in woodworking course, 1945; UA032.009.141.00016; Loesch, Russell T. (Box 141)
    - Pottery course, 1953; UA032.009.141.00017; Unknown (Box 141)
    - Recreational therapy, 1945; UA032.009.141.00018; Fay Foto (Box 141)
    - Practical therapy- tying a tie, 1955; UA032.009.141.00019; Unknown (Box 141)
    - Occupational therapy, 1945 -- 1955; UA032.009.141.00020; Unknown (Box 141)
    - Naval officer: patient interview, 1945 -- 1955; UA032.009.141.00021; Unknown (Box 141)
    - Children weaving, 1945 -- 1955; UA032.009.141.00022; Unknown (Box 141)
    - Occupational therapy instruction, 1945 -- 1955; UA032.009.141.00023; Unknown (Box 141)
    - Apprentice staff member and patient, 1945 -- 1955; UA032.009.141.00024; West Roxbury VA Photo (Box 141)
    - Pedal saw, 1945 -- 1955; UA032.009.141.00025 (Box 141)
    - Bedside activity: shellcraft, glove-making, weaving, 1945 -- 1955; UA032.009.141.00026 (Box 141)
    - Martha Wing Worcester State: class 24, 1937; UA032.009.141.00027 (Box 141)
    - WFOT banquet, 1962; UA032.009.141.00028 (Box 141)
    - Woodworking, weaving, bookbinding, 1948; UA032.009.141.00029 (Box 141)
    - People, 1964 -- 1968; UA032.009.141.00030 (Box 141)
    - Printing press, 1945; UA032.009.141.00031 (Box 141)
    - Bookbinding, 1945; UA032.009.141.00032 (Box 141)
    - Student and patient at the Boston School of Occupational Therapy working with toy blocks, 1970; UA032.009.DO.01415; McLaren, Lynn (Box Shared 47)
      This date is approximate.
      Students; Children; Patients; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Occupational therapy student and patient working with wood, 1945; UA032.009.DO.01416; Unknown (Box Shared 47)
      Students; Patients; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Occupational therapy student working with boy on walking, 1978; UA032.009.DO.01417; Morrow Christopher W. (Box Shared 47)
      Students; Patients; Children; Wheelchairs; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Helping hands at the Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1970; UA032.009.DO.01418; Unknown (Box Shared 47)
      Hand; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Occupational therapy student helping child at chalk board, 1970; UA032.009.DO.01419; Unknown (Box Shared 47)
      Students; Children; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Occupational therapy student helping patient at typewriter, 1970; UA032.009.DO.01420; Unknown (Box Shared 47)
      25. This date is approximate.
      Students; Typewriters; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Students at the Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1970; UA032.009.DO.01421; Unknown (Box Shared 48)
      This date is approximate. Identified on back (left to right): (bottom row) Sarah Coffin, Nan Ruter Katherine Feinbaum, Marcella Howe, Jacqueline Schroeder; (middle row) Virginia Hight, Betsy Shriber, Elaine Zimbelis, Sheri Rubens, Paula Fiorentino, Helen Wachtel; (top row) Sunny Stopper, Deborah Forman, Betsy Snider, Beth Fishner, Cindy Berman, Sue Miller, Joy Sambur, Martha Richards, Kirsten Sharke.
    - Occupational therapy students during classroom instruction, 1967; UA032.009.DO.01422; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 48)
      Students; Lectures or lecturing; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Occupational therapy students helping woman cut vegetables, 1966; UA032.009.DO.01423; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 48)
      Students; Women; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Occupational therapy student working on painting with young patient, 1962; UA032.009.DO.01424; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 48)
      Patients; Painting; Wheelchairs; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Occupational therapy students unwrapping patient's hand, 1964; UA032.009.DO.01425; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 48)
    - Occupational therapy student helping patient use saw, 1960; UA032.009.DO.01426; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 48)
    - Young boy and therapist at the Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1966; UA032.009.DO.01427; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 48)
      Patients; Children; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Occupational therapist and young boy working with blocks and string, 1966; UA032.009.DO.01428; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 48)
    - Students at the Boston School of Occupational Therapy reading papers in class, 1970; UA032.009.DO.01429; Bernstein, Dan (Box Shared 48)
      Students; photographic print; Boston School of Occupational Therapy
    - Student and patient at the Boston School of Occupational Therapy working with tiles, 1970; UA032.009.DO.01430; Unknown (Box Shared 48)
    - Occuational therapy student and young boy working with nuts and bolts, 1966; UA032.009.DO.01431; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 48)
  - BSOT Photographs, 1920 -- 1995; UA032.009.002
    - Formerly framed photographs, 1920 -- 1980; UA032.009.110.00001 (Box 110)
      Dates are approximate. Materials were removed from frames for preservation purposes.
    - Photographs, 1920 -- 1980; UA032.009.110.00002 (Box 110)
    - Photographs, 1940 -- 1989; UA032.009.110.00003 (Box 110)
    - Photographs, 1940 -- 1989; UA032.009.110.00004 (Box 110)
    - Encapsulated photographs, 1953 -- 1954; UA032.009.110.00005 (Box 110)
      Archivist attempted to remove photos from encapsulation but this process was stopped when it became apparent that damage to the images would occur.
    - Shepard Award and photo, 1963; UA032.009.110.00006 (Box 110)
      Letter was originally framed and photo was attached to frame.
    - Photo Exhibit, 1940 -- 1960; UA032.009.110.00007 (Box 110)
    - Mounted photographs, 1970 -- 1989; UA032.009.110.00008 (Box 110)
    - Mounted photographs, 1970 -- 1989; UA032.009.110.00009 (Box 110)
    - Mounted photographs, 1970 -- 1989; UA032.009.110.00010 (Box 110)
    - Lisa Sprung photo album of work with "Adam", 1970 -- 1980; UA032.009.110.00011 (Box 110)
    - Oversized photograph, 1970 -- 1989; UA032.009.110.00012 (Box 110)
    - Life Magazine, 1962; UA032.009.110.00013 (Box 110)
      Featuring article on the human body
    - Walnut Lodge - Extra slides, 1955 -- 1958; UA032.009.134.00001 (Box 134)
      slide (photograph)
    - Walnut Lodge - Extra slides, 1955 -- 1958; UA032.009.134.00002 (Box 134)
    - Walnut Lodge - Extra slides / Loesch slides, 1945 -- 1958; UA032.009.134.00003 (Box 134)
    - Walnut Lodge - Extra slides / Loesch slides, 1945 -- 1958; UA032.009.134.00004 (Box 134)
    - Walnut Lodge - Extra slides / Loesch slides, 1945 -- 1958; UA032.009.134.00005 (Box 134)
    - Walnut Lodge - Extra slides, 1955 -- 1958; UA032.009.134.00006 (Box 134)
    - Walnut Lodge - Extra slides, 1955 -- 1958; UA032.009.134.00007 (Box 134)
    - Walnut Lodge - Extra slides, 1955 -- 1958; UA032.009.134.00008 (Box 134)
    - OT computer technology, 1990 -- 1995; UA032.009.134.00009 (Box 134)
    - OT computer technology, 1990 -- 1995; UA032.009.134.00010 (Box 134)
    - Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA, 01-38, 1955 -- 1970; UA032.009.134.00011 (Box 134)
      Dates are approximate. Original label states: Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA - 100 slides - numbered 01-103 (no 02, 04, 07) 1 set - two scripts. This sheet contains slides 01 to 38. Slides 02, 04, 07, 10-17, 19, 20, 25, 27, 28, 31, and 32 are missing.
    - Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA, 39-61, 1955 -- 1970; UA032.009.134.00012 (Box 134)
      Dates are approximate. Original label states: Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA - 100 slides - numbered 01-103 (no 02, 04, 07) 1 set - two scripts. This sheet contains slides 39 to 61. Slides 45, 46 and 52 are missing.
    - Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA, 62-81, 1955 -- 1970; UA032.009.134.00013 (Box 134)
      Dates are approximate. Original label states: Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA - 100 slides - numbered 01-103 (no 02, 04, 07) 1 set - two scripts. This sheet contains slides 62 to 81.
    - Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA, 82-101, 1955 -- 1970; UA032.009.134.00014 (Box 134)
      Dates are approximate. Original label states: Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA - 100 slides - numbered 01-103 (no 02, 04, 07) 1 set - two scripts. This sheet contains slides 82 to 101.
    - Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA, 102-103, 1955 -- 1970; UA032.009.134.00015 (Box 134)
      Dates are approximate. Original label states: Prosthetic and sensory aids service - VA - 100 slides - numbered 01-103 (no 02, 04, 07) 1 set - two scripts. This sheet contains slides 102 and 103.
  - Instructional Videos, 1971 -- 1986; UA032.009.003
    - General Inhibition and Facilitation Techniques, 1971 -- 1986; UA032.009.135.00001 (Box UA032 Shared 3)
      Dates are approximate. Label states: General Inhibition and Facilitation Techniques, 30:00, Tufts University Boston School of Occupational Therapy. Preservation note: This video is on U-matic tape.
      videocassette
    - A Normal Baby, 1971 -- 1986; UA032.009.135.00002 (Box UA032 Shared 3)
      Dates are approximate. Label states: A Normal Baby: "The Sensory Motor Processes of the First Year", 40:00, Boston School of Occupational Therapy. Preservation note: This video is on U-matic tape.
    - PT-OT 27, 1971 -- 1986; UA032.009.135.00003 (Box UA032 Shared 3)
      Dates are approximate. Label states: PT-OT 27, 30:00, Tufts University. Preservation note: This video is on U-matic tape.
    - Evaluation of a child with a birth defect, 1971 -- 1986; UA032.009.135.00004 (Box UA032 Shared 3)
      Dates are approximate. Label states: Evaluation of a child with a birth defect, 30:00, Boston School of Occupational Therapy. Preservation note: This video is on U-matic tape.
    - Part I and II, 1971 -- 1986; UA032.009.135.00005 (Box UA032 Shared 3)
      Dates are approximate. May not contain footage related to BSOT. Label states: Part I and II, 33:00, Tufts University. Preservation note: This video is on U-matic tape.
  - Lantern Slides and glass negatives, 1921 -- 1939; UA032.009.004
    - Patient weaving a basket, 1925; UA032.009.138.00001; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #1.
      Occupational therapy; Basket making; lantern slide
    - Patients drawing in their beds [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00002; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #2.
      Occupational therapy; Arts; Drawing; lantern slide
    - Man working with small loom, 1925; UA032.009.138.00003; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Occupational therapy; Weaving; lantern slide
    - Patients working on individual projects, 1925; UA032.009.138.00004; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #4.
      Occupational therapy; Hospital patients; lantern slide
    - Man at a typewriter [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00005; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #4. It is missing a frame, and is cracked on one side.
      Occupational therapy; Typewriters; lantern slide
    - Patients drawing in their beds [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00006; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #5. This is a duplicate of UA032.009.138.00002.
    - Man weaving a basket with nurse, 1925; UA032.009.138.00007; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #5 1/2.
      Occupational therapy; Basket making; Nurses; lantern slide
    - Five seated men working on projects with nurse assisting man with loom [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00008; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #6.
      Occupational therapy; Nurses; Weaving; lantern slide
    - Patient with hand brace using small loom [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00009; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #7. It is cracked in two places. A duplicate exists at UA032.009.139.00016.
      Occupational therapy; Beadwork; Orthopedic apparatus; lantern slide
    - Two Navy patients at work on occupational therapy projects [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00010; Unknown (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #8. This is a duplicate of UA032.009.139.00018.
      Occupational therapy; Nurses; Metal-work (Handicraft); lantern slide; U.S. Navy
    - Man braiding a leather belt [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00011; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #9. A duplicate slide exists in UA032.009.139.00020.
      Occupational therapy; Weaving; Leatherwork; lantern slide
    - Man carving in wood [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00012; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #10. A duplicate exists at UA032.009.139.00017.
      Occupational therapy; Woodwork; lantern slide
    - Two men weaving at large looms [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00013; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #11.
    - Workshop with nurses and patients, 1925; UA032.009.138.00014; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Occupational therapy; Nurses; lantern slide
    - Man at typewriter [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00015; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #14. This is a duplicate of UA032.009.138.00004.
    - Seated man working at small loom, 1925; UA032.009.138.00016; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #15.
    - Man with prosthetic hook at loom, 1925; UA032.009.138.00017; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Occupational therapy; Weaving; Orthopedic apparatus; lantern slide
    - Patient in woodshop [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00018; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #16.
      Occupational therapy; Woodwork; Amputees; lantern slide
    - Five seated men working on projects with nurse assisting man with loom [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00019; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #17. Duplicate of UA032.009.138.00008.
    - Man at pedal saw [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00020; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #17.
      Occupational therapy; Woodwork; Barrier-free design; lantern slide
    - Walter Reed General Hospital [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00021; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #18. The label: Walter Reid General Hospital was found on the original negative for this slide. This is a duplicate of UA032.009.138.00028.
      Occupational therapy; Woodwork; lantern slide; Walter Reed Army Hospital (Washington, D.C.)
    - Man using chisel at woodworking bench [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00022; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #19.
    - Two men weaving at large looms [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00023; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #20. It is a duplicate of UA032.009.138.00013.
    - Man at pedal saw [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00024; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #21. Duplicate of UA032.009.138.00020.
    - Side view of man at pedal saw, 1925; UA032.009.138.00025; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #21.
    - Child with cast weaving, 1925; UA032.009.138.00026; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Occupational therapy; Children; Weaving; lantern slide
    - Female patients seated in a circle, 1925; UA032.009.138.00027; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #22.
      Occupational therapy; Women patients; lantern slide
    - Walter Reed General Hospital [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00028; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #22. The label: Walter Reid General Hospital was found on the original negative for this slide. This is a duplicate of UA032.009.138.00021.
    - Female patients with wood blocks [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00029; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #23.
    - Man using chisel at woodworking bench [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00030; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #23a. This is a duplicate of UA032.009.138.00022.
    - Man using drill - Walter Reed General Hospital [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00031; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #23b.
    - Seated women working on individual projects [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00032; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #24.
    - Man standing in field [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00033; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #25.
      Occupational therapy; Outdoor recreation; lantern slide
    - Patient in woodshop [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00034; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #26. This is a duplicate of UA032.009.138.00018.
    - Man at pedal-operated spinning wheel, 1925; UA032.009.138.00035; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #27. A similar image exists in UA032.009.139.00010.
      Occupational therapy; Spinning-wheel; lantern slide
    - Group of men with bundles of sticks, 1925; UA032.009.138.00036; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #27.
    - Man working with clay [Copy 1], 1925; UA032.009.138.00037; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #28. A duplicate slide exists at UA032.009.139.00011.
      Occupational therapy; Clay--Therapeutic use; lantern slide
    - Seated female patient, 1925; UA032.009.138.00038; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #29.
    - Seated female patient rolling cloth, 1925; UA032.009.138.00039; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #30.
    - Patient shown in two shots: weaving at a loom and in distress on the floor, 1925; UA032.009.138.00040; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #31. This appears to be the same patient pictured in UA032.009.138.00038.
    - Seated female sewing, 1925; UA032.009.138.00041; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #32.
      Occupational therapy; Women patients; Sewing; lantern slide
    - Child with cast weaving [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00042; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #32. This is a duplicate of UA032.009.138.00026.
    - Close-up of a patient's hands, 1925; UA032.009.138.00043; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #33.
      Occupational therapy; Patients; lantern slide
    - Man standing in field [Copy 2], 1925; UA032.009.138.00045; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #34. This is a duplicate of UA032.009.138.00033.
    - Female seated at table, 1925; UA032.009.138.00046; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #34.
    - Male patients gathering bundles of sticks, 1925; UA032.009.138.00047; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)
      Date is approximate. This slide is labeled #36.
    - Male patients weaving baskets, 1925; UA032.009.138.00048; Thurston, John H. (Box 138)